[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does the ghost of Bloody Mary appear when summoned according to a popular urban legend?", "correct_answer": "In the mirror", "incorrect_answers": ["On the roof", "In the closet", "Behind a closed door"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the United States, which of the following doctors is likely to make the most money?", "correct_answer": "Radiologist", "incorrect_answers": ["Neurologist", "General Internist", "Psychiatrist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People can be voluntarily euthanised in the world depicted in Soylent Green. How is euthanasia referred to in the movie?", "correct_answer": "Going home", "incorrect_answers": ["Going to the sleep", "Going into the field", "Returning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie made in 2002 and directed by Denzel Washington tugged at our heartstrings while we watched a young man deal with his abusive past.", "correct_answer": "Antwone Fisher", "incorrect_answers": ["The Great Debaters", "Pride", "Training Day"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This mathematician was the first to develop an algebraic method of solving any cubic equation.", "correct_answer": "Nicolai Fontana Tartaglia", "incorrect_answers": ["Evariste Galois", "Girolamo Cardano", "Carl Friedrich Gauss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This property of the cell membrane allows allows some particles to cross more easily than others.", "correct_answer": "Selective permeability", "incorrect_answers": ["Discriminative passage", "Semi-permeability", "Semi-discriminative"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the distance between the planets and the Sun, Jupiter is situated between which two planets in the Solar system?", "correct_answer": "Mars and Saturn", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercury and Venus", "Venus and Earth", "Neptune and Pluto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1993 the Scottish hotel-owner Campbell Aird received a bionic organ, which was the first of its kind. This is the organ.", "correct_answer": "Arm", "incorrect_answers": ["Ear", "Leg", "Eye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the flea, a well-known external parasite?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They have laterally compressed bodies.", "They dont have wings.", "They live on mammals and birds."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning actress starred in the 1981 movie On Golden Pond?", "correct_answer": "Katharine Hepburn", "incorrect_answers": ["Meryl Streep", "Susan Sarandon", "Elizabeth Taylor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is true about the sources of vitamin B5?", "correct_answer": "It is found in a large variety of foods.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is found only in plant products.", "It is synthesized in the skin under the influence of the sun rays.", "It is found only in animal products."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the word fish both a noun and a verb?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}]